{"data":[{"question":"Stacy is tall; ___, she is beautiful.","a":"besides","b":"beside","c":"and","d":"but","answer":"1","explain":"- Besides: in addition to someone or something else that is being mentioned","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"There was a ___ talk among the eight countries last month.","a":"friendship","b":"friend","c":"really","d":"friendly","answer":"4","explain":"- Friendly (adj): goes before a noun (talk)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"___ explanation is necessary.","a":"Further","b":"Farther","c":"Furthest","d":"Farthest","answer":"1","explain":"- Further: used for talking about an additional thing or amount","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The bananas taste ___ and sell ___.","a":"good, good","b":"well, well","c":"well, good","d":"good, well","answer":"4","explain":".","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Elizabeth is frightened that she ___ knows what to do.","a":"almost","b":"nearly","c":"hardly","d":"mostly","answer":"3","explain":".","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"There is a ___ door behind the bookshelf.","a":"hidden","b":"hide","c":"hiding","d":"hid","answer":"1","explain":"- Hidden (adj): not easy to find","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"You will be late for school if you don't put on your clothes ___.","a":"soon","b":"fast","c":"quickly","d":"rapidly","answer":"3","explain":"- We use quickly(adverb) after put on","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Please don't speak so ___.","a":"quick","b":"soon","c":"fastly","d":"fast","answer":"4","explain":"- Speak so fast","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"The buses run every ___ minutes in rush hours.","a":"a few","b":"few","c":"other","d":"many","answer":"2","explain":"- Every few: some, but not many","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"What a surprise that Wesley has made ___ friends since he just joined the club.","a":"only a few","b":"quite a few","c":"quite a little","d":"a few","answer":"2","explain":"- Quite a few + countable nouns","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"}]}